<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ResInsight</title>
    <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ResInsight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2019.04</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/whats-new/releasenotes_2019_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/whats-new/releasenotes_2019_04/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight 2019.04 is the latest version of ResInsight, the professional quality, open source 3D visualization, curve plotting and post-processing tool for Eclipse reservoir models. Version 2019.04 contains a larger number of new and exciting features, some of which are listed below.
Grid Cross Plots ResInsight supports the creation of cross plots of two results against each other, with each cell in the grid representing one data point in the plot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testimonials</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/testimonials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/testimonials/</guid>
      <description>“I have been using ResInsight now for some time and have stopped using the commercial software as ResInsight is much more responsive and easier to use. It really is an excellent piece of software.”
David Baxendale
Senior Petroleum Engineering Advisor, RPS Energy
&amp;ldquo;ResInsight is an excellent tool to visualize simulation results and offers good-looking and illustrative graphs for presentations. I found the integration with Octave especially powerful in my research.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2018.11</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/whats-new/releasenotes_2018_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/whats-new/releasenotes_2018_11/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight 2018.11 is the latest version of ResInsight, the professional quality, open source 3D visualization, curve plotting and post-processing tool for Eclipse reservoir models. Version 2018.11 contains a larger number of new and exciting features, some of which are listed below.
Local Grid Refinement (LGR) Local Grid Refinement (LGR) can be created based on Eclipse simulations. The refined grids can also be visualised in 3D.
See Completions LGR
Well Path Creation ResInsight lets the user create new/custom well paths by clicking in the 3D view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Instructions</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/buildinstructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/buildinstructions/</guid>
      <description>Source code The source code is hosted at GitHub
In a git enabled shell do: git clone https://github.com/OPM/ResInsight.git
Dependencies and Prerequisites Windows Compiler Visual Studio 2015 or later is supported.
GCC Compiler GCC version 4.9 or later is supported. On RedHat Linux 6 you need to install devtoolset-3, and enable it with
source /opt/rh/devtoolset-3/enable  Qt4 Qt Qt4 version 4.6.2 or later is supported. On Windows we recommend Qt-4.8.7, while the default installation will do under Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notification Subscription</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/releasenotification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/more/releasenotification/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn Feel free to join ResInsight on LinkedIn
Newsletter By subscribing to the Release Notification you will get notified when new releases are available. Please use the button below to send a request for subscription mail.
Subscribe</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>